What is the most important thing?
Do you have any recommendations for beauty products for uncles?
It's a moment when you can really let yourself go.
It's a moment when you can really let yourself go, and it's something you can do with a smile on your face and enjoy.
I think it's an important element.
I want to get better at making small talk.
I've heard that the best people at work are good at making small talk.
What is your favorite snack?
Kettle and idols
Hello, I'm Kettle, from the freezing room of Stardust.
I'm Ayaka Yasumoto, attendance number 5 from Shiritsu Ebisu Chugaku.
First of all, congratulations on the 15th anniversary of Shiritsu Ebisu Chugaku.
And to kick things off, on January 6th and 7th, we held the New Year's Grand Performance.
How do you feel about it looking back?
Well, this was the first time in a long time for Shiritsu Ebisu Chugaku to hold a New Year's Grand Performance.
We usually perform at the end of the year, but this was the first time in a while that we performed at the beginning of the year.
We wanted to bring something fun and uplifting to the people of Japan, so we performed for two days and had a lot of fun.
I think we had a lot of fun at the concert.
That's great!
And now, Ebichu...
It's been a little over a year since the current members came together.
Yes.
The two newly joined members, Emayuna and...
I've often taken energetic videos of them here at Kanto Idol.
What do you think of them from your point of view?
Well, yes...
They're... well... every time a new member joins the group...
I'm the type of person who gets a little shy and it takes me a while to get to know people.
But with Emma and Yuna, I feel like we have a similar vibe.
Especially Emma, I felt the same kind of vibe.
We've been going out to eat together, and we've become good friends.
Yes, yes, yes.
Mr. Sakurai...
He talks to me so smilingly.
I get caught up in it and before I know it, I'm smiling too.
That's right.
Yuna's dance teacher told her to smile and smile and smile.
Maybe I'm not aware of it.
I don't think she's aware of it, but she's trying to ask me something.
I'm thinking about it.
When I try my best to make eye contact with him, he notices it and smiles, lifting the corners of his mouth with his hands like this.
He corrects me.
They're both smiling, and it's adorable.
They are smiling, aren't they?
And Yakan-kun, there are still some things I'm not familiar with about Yakamoto-san, so I'll leave it at that.
So I went to the official YouTube page of Seizu Ebisu Chugaku.
I had a chance to watch the video "Yasumoto Ayaka's Question" on the official YouTube page of Seitsu Ebisu Chugaku, and I found it very interesting.
Thank you very much.
In the video, you mentioned that you use 4 different toothpastes.
Do you still use different types of toothpaste?
Yes, I still do.
Do you have a different toothpaste for each of them?
One in the morning and one at night.
It depends on my oral environment at the time.
I just want to clean it really well.
I want to get rid of stains.
If you want to get rid of mouth odor
I often use the standard minty ones sold in drugstores.
If you want to whiten your mouth, use a strong minty one.
If you want to whiten your mouth
There are two patterns
There are two types of whitening products
Whitening effect type
and the other is the type that can cleanse and whiten
and the other is the type that can cleanse while whitening well.
The whitening effect is different depending on the condition of your teeth at the time.
depending on the condition of my teeth at the time.
Are there any plans to add new members in the future?
Yes, we do.
I'm planning to go to Korea soon.
I've already checked out a toothpaste in Korea.
I've already checked out a toothpaste in Korea and I'm definitely going to buy it.
Is it a different type?
It's a different type of toothpaste with a whitening effect.
It's a whitening effect, but there are about five different levels.
There's a toothpaste that has 5 different whitening levels.
I'm going to check the color of my teeth and buy it.
I'm thinking of buying it.
I'm going to buy a new kind of toothpaste.
The toothpaste will have its own personality.
Blah, blah, blah.
Yes, sir.
Oh, wow.
I almost told him I'd buy it when we were talking.
Really?
This show is...
Mr. Ietate Neezo.
Mr. Slow
Miyuki
Ebitai-san
This program was provided by Shinchanmaru-san!
Thank you very much!